autoworld.com.my 2004-06-04

# Autoworld - Help Guide

This Statement of Privacy applies to the web site of autoworld.com.my (â€œSiteâ€), an automotive portal service provided by Autoweb Sdn.Bhd. (â€œAWSBâ€). Our postal and office address is :- 

> Autoweb Sdn Bhd (Co. No. 323199-A)  
>  Level 3A, Wisma Hong Leong,  
>  18 Jalan Perak,  
>  50450 Kuala Lumpur,  
>  Malaysia. 
> 
> Tel : 603-2169-2074  
>  Fax.: 603-2169-2815 
> 
> E-mail : [support@autoworld.com.my](mailto:support@autoworld.com.my)

As a fully internet based company which provides web services to the public, AWSB is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following to fully understand our practices regarding the use of your personal information. By using the Site, you consent to the data practices described herein. 

This policy applies specifically to your name, e-mail address, telephone number, and any other individually identifiable information which we collect from our users. 

**What We Collect**

ÂÂ  AWSBâ€™s general policy is to only collect individually identifiable information that is absolutely necessary for the transaction or useful for our own internal operations. During the registration process and creation of an account, for accountability purposes, we do require a user's full name, e-mail address, telephone contact, residential or office address, date of birth, gender, occupation and Identity Card/Passport number. 

ÂÂ  We record the e-mail addresses and messages of those who post messages, photographs, communications and comments or feedback on the Site, or who communicate with us via e-mail. 

ÂÂ  We also record aggregate information on what pages users access or visit, information volunteered by users and merchants, such as survey information and/or Site registration data, and the e-mail address of merchants, buyers, sellers and bidders on the Site. 

ÂÂ  We will also track certain particulars about you. This information includes the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Site or not), browser type, access times, the pages you visit and your IP address. Many sites automatically collect this information using widely available site web statistical tools. 

ÂÂ  If you choose to bid, buy or sell on our Site, we collect information about your bidding, buying and selling behaviour. 

ÂÂ  We also collect your credit cards details and billing address (if applicable). 

**Cookies**

We use cookies on certain pages of our Site. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Site. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. 

We let the advertisers on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companiesâ€™ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not AWSBâ€™s Privacy Policy. Other companies do not have access to our cookies, and we do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the other companies. 

**What We Do With Information Collected**

ÂÂ  We collect and use your information to operate the Site and deliver the services you have requested, including the following : 

(i) customising the advertising and content you see;  
(ii) fulfil your requests for, or to inform you of, products and services;  
(iii) improve our services;  
(iv)Â Â Â contact you;  
(v)Â Â Â Â bill you (where applicable);  
(vi)Â Â Â conduct research/surveys;  
(vii)Â Â provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients;  
(viii)Â resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems;  
(ix)Â Â Â enforce our terms and conditions for using the Site;   
(x)Â Â Â Â for order fulfilment purposes, where we need to provide your name, address, telephone contact and/or e-mail address to our dealers and/or external parties to enable delivery/collection of merchandise. 

ÂÂ  We do not sell, lease or share our customer or member lists to other parties. We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personally identifiable information (e.g. e-mail, name, address, telephone number, Identity Card number) is not transferred to the third party. We may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you e-mail or postal mail, provide customer support or arrange for deliveries. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to us, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

ÂÂ  We will disclose your information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to : 

(i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us or this Site; 

(ii) protect and defend the rights or property of AWSB and this Site; 

(iii) enforce the terms and conditions of use of this Site; 

(iv) investigate , prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the personal safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law; and 

(v) act under exigent circumstances to protect the interests of our users, this Site or others. 

ÂÂ  We transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. 

**Collection of photocopy of Identity Card/Passport (where applicable)**

Where applicable, AWSB may require a photocopy or faxed copy of your Identity Card/Passport before you can access to or use certain services on the Site. 

This Site is a site where the identities of a member are important. This helps reduce fraud between members and enhance credibility. 

AWSB assures all members that photocopies and details of Identity Card/Passport are kept securely by us and will never be used for marketing purposes or disclosed or given to any third party by electronic means or print, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**Option to Create a Public Profile**

In the Community Section, we give you an option to create a public profile of yourself by clicking on the â€œAbout Meâ€ link, containing personal information that you have volunteered about yourself so that other members or users in the Community Section and other public areas can learn something about you. Everything you enter in your public profile will be visible to the public. You may edit or delete your information in your public profile at any time by going to the â€œAbout Meâ€ link. 

While participating in the Community Section or other public areas, we advise you against giving out personally identifiable information to strangers online, which they may use for illegal or harmful purposes. 

**Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information**

You can update or edit your personal information at any time by clicking on the â€œMy Accountâ€ link. 

We reserve the right to send you marketing communications and communications relating to the Services, such as service announcements, administrative messages and newsletters, from time to time. However, all communications will contain information on how to unsubscribe from that e-mail list. In the event that you receive an e-mail that you think is unsolicited, please e-mail us at [support@autoworld.com.my](mailto:support@autoworld.com.my), and we will make every effort to have your e-mail address removed from future mailings. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may, in our sole discretion, modify, update or revise this Privacy Policy at any time, and you agree to be bound by these modifications or revisions. The amended terms shall automatically become effective upon posting on our Site. Your continued access to or use of this Site after such change shall constitute your (i) acknowledgement of this Privacy Policy, as modified/revised from time to time; and (ii) your consent to abide and be bound by this Privacy Policy, as modified/revised from time to time. 

This Privacy Policy, as modified/revised from time to time, is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the autoworld.com.my User Agreement. 

We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information. 

This Privacy Policy was last revised on 9th January 2003.
